# Martin Reboredo

# **Frontend Web Developer**

**EU/ Spanish Nationality** 

Madrid +34 677 28 37 16 contacto@martinreboredo.com www.martinReboredo.com

+3 years of Web Development experience, designing, creating and supervising responsive websites, CMS, landing pages, and ads. I worked for different startups and industries. Thanks to my business development background I always take into account the business impact and the branding guidelines. My goal is to deliver meaningful experiences and to work with an amazing team of people where I can develop my full potential.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Web Developer

www.aguafy.com, Remote, 2016-Present

Created Online Business Strategy that included a marketing plan and the development of the website with several landing pages for Ads.

- Render optimization and cross browser compatibility with a 100% responsive interface and optimized UX/UI and SEO/SEM
- Google Map API, Zoho Chat, Google Analytics scripts, etc..
- Save budget and time by 70% by implementing cost-saving initiatives.

#### **Marketing Manager**

www.playbusiness.mx, Mexico City, 2016-2017

Lead a Marketing Team of 5 extraordinary people. Play Business is the biggest Equity Crowdfunding Firm and Company Builder in LATAM.

- Product Development using Agile/Scrum methodology, MVPs
- Launched Marketing Campaigns with 20% visitors growth monthly rate.

#### Webmaster

www.exclusivasfaro.com, Mexico City, 2013-2016

Created and implemented the company online presence. Improvement in organizational tasks and processes using different technologies (ERP, Cloud, Mail Service, GPS, Google Drive, Responsive Web development, Prestashop, etc...).

- +400% ROI in implemented strategy and +5% sales growth
- +100% new customer growth rate.

### Cofounder

Info Party London, UK, 2006-2013

Lead Ads and Promotions Agency with more than 20 associates, organizing simultaneously marketing and Digital Ads campaigns for 14 clients.

#### **SKILLS**

**Programing Languages** 

HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript ES6

Frameworks, Libraries and pre-processors

Bootstrap, JQuery, SASS, PostCSS, Babel

(Currently learning MEARN stack)

#### Tools & Tech

- Github, Chrome DevTools, cPanel, FTP,
- HTTP, AJAX, JSON, APIs
- Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, XD
- Google Adwords & Analytics, Webmaster
- Npm, Gulp, Web Pack, Command Line ...

#### Methodology

Agile/Scrum, UX/UI, SEO, SEM, Lean startup,

#### **CMS**

Prestashop & Woocommerce & Wordpress

#### **Speaking Languages**

English 100%, Spanish 100%, Portuguese 50%

# **HIGHLIGHTS**

- Authored article in **Expansión** magazine (MX).
- Taught Marketing in **Anahuac University**
- **Experience in Startups and Crowdfunding**

# **EDUCATION**

Fullstack Web Development, (present) freeCodeCamp, Udemy, LinkedIN, MOOC's.

Master in Business Administration, (2013)

University of Roehampton, London, UK. Metropolitan University, London, UK.

**Bachelor of Business Administration**, (2004)

University of Wales, IESIDE, Vigo, Spain.